Jamie Leviner

Software Engineer Born 1980 in Florence, SC





Experience

Software Engineer

ACS Technologies July 2017 - present

Programming and watching cute cat videos.

Software Engineer-Associate

ACS Technologies July 2016 - July 2017 Fulfillment of extremely important tasks.

Software Development Apprentice

ACS Technologies August 2015 - July 2016 Making coffee and baking cookies.

Intern

ACS Technologies May 2015 - August 2016



Education

B.S. in Computer Science, Minor in Applied Mathematics January 2011 - December 2014 Francis Marion University, Florence, SC 29501

Projects

best-resume-ever

Vue



jamieleviner.com

Jekyll

My personal website. Created using the jekyll theme Jalpc.

About me

For the past 5 years, I have worked as a full stack software engineer with a concentration on front-end architecture, frameworks, and tooling. I am strongly interested in becoming part of a development culture that improves and enables its people, and I am looking forward to facing some new challenges.

Skills



Contact



levinerjamie@gmail.com



jamieleviner.com

